(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
右に進むか…
Should I go right...?
左の道なら…
If I take the left path...
解は？
The solution?
チャンス？
A chance?
リスクがでかい
High risk.
リスクが小さい
Low risk.
やっぱり右？
Right after all?
人を過度に信じないように 愛さないように 期待しないように
To not trust people excessively, to not love, to not expect anything.
かと言って角が立たないように 気取らぬように 目立たぬように
But also to not ruffle feathers, to not be pretentious, to not stand out.
誰一人傷つけぬように 虐めぬように 殺さぬように
To not hurt anyone, to not bully, to not kill.
かと言って偽善がバレないように 威張らないように
But also so the hypocrisy isn't revealed, to not be arrogant.
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
To not forget light jokes and lip service.
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
To smile at all times and sprinkle charm.
ビターチョコデコレーション とかく言わずにちゃんと召し上がれ
Bitter Choco Decoration, eat it up properly without complaining.
ビターチョコデコレーション 食わず嫌いはちゃんと治さなきゃ
Bitter Choco Decoration, you must fix your pickiness.
頭空っぽその後に残る心が本物なら
If the heart that remains after emptying your head is real,
きっと君だって同じ事
Surely you are the same.
そこで一つここで今すぐ現実
One thing there, right here, right now, reality...
いいや
No, wait.
元の味が晒されるように
So that the original taste is exposed,
瀕するように
So that it's on the verge of death,
分かるように
So that it's understood.
被せた口は閉ざさるように
So that the covered mouth stays shut,
笑わすように
So as to make you laugh,
笑われるように
So as to be laughed at.
人ちゃんと敬うように
So that I respect people properly,
崇めるように
So that I worship them,
讃えるように
So that I praise them.
決して邪魔にならないように
So that I never become a nuisance,
ふざけないように
So that I don't fool around.
集団参加の終止形
The terminal form of group participation,
またへこらへこら言っちゃって
Bowing and scraping again,
「あれ前髪超絶最強じゃん」
"Oh, your bangs are super the best!"
とかどうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Saying things I don't care about at all.
毎朝毎晩もう一回
Every morning, every night, one more time,
宗教的社会の集団です
It's a religious social group.
決して発狂しないように
So as never to go insane.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
Sometimes lonely love stains you.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
立つ鳥のあと き立つ
A bird leaving the water makes a scene,
クソのあと
After the shit.
初めは数多居そうな
At first, like one of the many,
大言壮語並べたが
I lined up big words and boasting, but...
いやよいやよも好きのうち
"No means no" is also part of liking it.
いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
Well, my goodness, today is the first time...
こんなとはね 君センスあるよ
I didn't expect this. You have sense.
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
In the season of love, Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
With feelings of love, Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Longing for the ideal that everyone desires.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
個性や情は全部焼き払い
Burn away all individuality and emotion.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Kill greed and ego, and bury them in the earth.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration.
僕は大人にやっとなったよママ
I finally became an adult, Mama.
明日もきっとこの先も
Tomorrow and surely beyond that,
地獄は続くどこまでも
Hell continues everywhere.
あぁだからどうか今だけは
Ah, so please, just for now,
子供の頃の気持ちのままで
Let me stay with the feelings of my childhood.
一切合切忘れてやってこうぜ
Let's forget absolutely everything and go for it!
あぁ思い出した
Ah, I remembered.
あぁあの時の
Ah, that time's...
気真面目な
Seriousness...
やっぱいいや
Never mind.
サイコロ...
A die...
5が出た
A five came out.
ん？何これ？
Hm? What's this?
椅子？
A chair?
One, two, one, two, three, four!
泡と化した世の常
The way of the world turned into bubbles,
屑引いたって動じない
Even if I draw trash, I'm not shaken.
肝心なのは Strong mind
What's essential is a strong mind.
出し抜いて Survive
Outwit and survive.
行き着く先は
The destination is...
Heaven or Hell
この世界のルール
The rules of this world,
たった一つ
There is only one:
勝者こそが正義
The winner is justice.
女は度胸
Women need guts,
ちらつかせるの
Flaunting it.
あいつの
That guy's...
やれること何だってやる
I'll do whatever I can.
あたしは賭け狂いの Queen
I am the gambling crazy Queen.
お見通しだよ Honey
I can see right through it, Honey,
読み切ってるでしょ？
You've read it all, right?
Deal with the devil 見透かして
Deal with the devil, see through it,
あたしのモノにする
And make it mine.
あなたの髪の 一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair.
A million dollars, I'd say raise
震えているわ Boy
You're shaking, Boy.
降ろさせはしないわ
I won't let you fold.
Deal with the devil 強行突破
Deal with the devil, forced breakthrough.
たまらないスリル
Unbearable thrill.
誰にも触らせない
I won't let anyone touch,
この Money
This money.
A million dollars, I'd say raise
さあ Com'on 覚悟きめたら
Now come on, if you've made up your mind,
震え高ぶれ My heart
Tremble and get high, my heart.
欲しがるようじゃね
If you want it,
まだ Baby
You're still a Baby.
誰にも負けない感じさせて Love me honey
Make me feel like I won't lose to anyone, Love me honey.
あなたの正体は...
Your true identity is...
キミ吊って甘い罠
I'll lure you in with a sweet trap,
仕掛けて罠にハメるわ
set it up and catch you in it.
油断誘うのよ
I'll invite your negligence.
仕込まれた TRAP & CHEAT
A set-up TRAP & CHEAT.
何も知らないような顔で
With a face that knows nothing,
落とすわ アナタを
I will take you down.
聞かせて それ優等生？
Tell me, is that an honor student?
夢見てるんでしょ？
You're dreaming, aren't you?
で どうやったって変更は効かない
So, no matter what you do, changes won't work.
どんな小さなズルだって
No matter how small the cheat,
私の目は誤魔化されないわ
my eyes won't be deceived.
自惚れた開いた口塞ぐ
I'll shut your conceited, gaping mouth.
カッコつけるのはウンザリ
I'm sick of you acting cool.
粛清してあげる
I'll purge you.
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let my targeted prey escape.
唇 濡らして頂くわ 愛で
I'll wet my lips and partake, with love.
ダイヤのジャックで手が揃うわ
With the Jack of Diamonds, my hand is complete.
笑みは凍り 始末だけ
The smile freezes, only disposal remains.
私のポーカーフェイスは It's perfect
My poker face is It's perfect.
一部の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show even a fraction of a gap.
視線 感じてるわ
I feel your gaze.
お望み通りの最後マデ
Until the very end you wished for.
見てばかり居ないで
Don't just stand there watching,
あたしが教えてイクから
I will teach you myself.
負けるのが怖いの？
Are you afraid of losing?
いい気・減
How pathetic.
夢見てるんでしょ？
You're dreaming, aren't you?
で どうやったって変更は効かない
So, no matter what you do, changes won't work.
あたしのモノにする
I'll make you mine.
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair, all of it.
自惚れた開いた口には
Into that conceited, gaping mouth,
恐怖を与えてあげるわ
I will feed you fear.
底までイクわ
I'll go to the very bottom.
で どうやったって
So, no matter what you do,
躊躇わない スリル
I won't hesitate, thrill.
誰にも触らせない
I won't let anyone touch,
この Money!
this Money!
ダイヤのジャックで手が揃うわ
With the Jack of Diamonds, my hand is complete.
覚悟決めて
Prepare yourself,
ハイになるまで打って
bet until you get high.
震える指じゃ もてあそべないわ
You can't play with trembling fingers.
誰にも負けない感じさせて
Make me feel like I won't lose to anyone.
Love me!
はっ…あれ？椅子…なくなっちゃった。
Huh? Oh? The chair... is gone.
あぁ…もう少し座らせて欲しかった。
Ah... I wanted to sit a little longer.
はーい みんな！見えてる？聞こえてる？
Hi everyone! Can you see me? Can you hear me?
ホロライブ所属の癒し系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです。
I'm Hololive's healing-type Half-Elf, AkiRose also known as Aki Rosenthal.
ハロハロハロー！
Hello hello hello!
アローナ！
Alona!
はー えー 今回の…アキロゼ生誕祭2026へようこそ！
Haa, um, welcome to... AkiRose Birthday Celebration 2026!
早速ね、なんか色々行われていたんですが…
Something was already going on right away, but...
一体今回のライブはどうなっちゃうのか
what is going to happen in this concert exactly?
是非最後まで、必見…お見逃しなくお願いします。
Please, it's a must-watch until the end... don't miss it.
今回のライブのハッシュタグは #アキロゼ生誕祭2026
The hashtag for this concert is #AkiRoseBirthday2026
こちらを付けてXに沢山ポストしてね。
Please add this and post a lot on X.
勿論 可愛いスクショ…
Of course, lots of cute screenshots...
えーのも沢山撮って
take lots of nice ones too,
合わせて投稿して下さい。
and please post them together.
ライブが終わったらアキロゼ見に行きます…見てね。
AkiRose will go look at them after the live ends... so watch me.
あ、チャンネル登録もよろしくね。
Ah, please subscribe to the channel too.
OK？
Ok?
はいありがとう。
Yes, thank you.
ん？何だ？何何何？
Hm? What is it? What what what?
ていうか、ここ何処なんだろう…
I mean, where is this place...
ん？お？あんなとこにルーレットがある。
Hm? Oh? There's a roulette over there.
え？回るのかな？
Eh? Does it spin?
回った！えーすごい！おー回った…
It spun! Eh, amazing! Oh, it spun...
えっ？おっ？えっ？
Eh? Oh? Eh?
何？何？
What? What is it?
どうなっちゃうの？
What's going to happen?
えっ？あっ…えぇ？
Eh? Ah... Eeeh?
ピース？
Peace?
ん？
Hmm?
なんだ？
What is this?
A-Happy
悩める人の
For those who are troubled,
A-Lucky
隣り合うもの
Things that sit side by side.
Be-Happy
絶えず目指せよ
Constantly aim for it,
生きているんだし
Since you're alive after all.
ねえ、恐れした過去も
Hey, the past you feared,
退屈な未来も
and the boring future too,
カウンセリング、ギャレギャレ
Counseling, gal-gal,
古今東西、ピースピース！
All times and places, Peace Peace!
A-Happy
A-Lucky
Be-Happy
UNDEAD
ねえねえねえねえ
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
何だかどうして
Somehow, why is it
戦ってるような
That it feels like we're fighting?
そんな気がするの
I get that feeling.
逃げられない
Can't run away,
出たくもない
Don't even want to leave,
不幸な自分？
My unhappy self?
否
No,
とっくに死んでる
I'm already long dead.
透明な亡霊
A transparent ghost,
大決定、大決定
It's decided, it's decided,
言いたい記憶の
Memories I want to say
Knock out！
Knock out!
残念
Too bad,
もういないのに
Even though I'm gone,
あれ？そっちはアイロニー
Huh? That side is irony.
ねえ、透かされてる
Hey, being seen right through,
のは今の自分
That's my current self.
ナンセンス
Nonsense,
消えないレッテル
Labels that won't disappear,
嫌よコンプレックス
I hate it, this complex.
取り憑かれてるみたい
It's like I'm possessed,
巻き付いたまま
Still wrapped around me.
まだ
Still
離れない
won't let go,
在りし日の自分
My past self.
UNDEAD
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead yet,
終わんない負の連鎖
This unending chain of negativity.
生きてるかどうかも
Whether I'm alive or not,
分かり続けなかった
I kept failing to understand.
不条理に甘んじて
Accepting the absurdity,
満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied with it.
幸せになろうとしないなんて
Not trying to be happy is...
嫌だ
I hate it.
この世、この世は
This world, this world is
奇怪奇怪ファンタジー
A bizarre, bizarre fantasy.
次は鬼が出るか
Will a demon appear next?
蛇が出るか
Or will a snake appear?
出会って、あって
We met, we met,
やっと始まる物語
And finally the story begins.
さあきっと化け物
Surely, the monsters
ぞろぞろ兄弟、ピースピース！
Are all brothers here, Peace Peace!
Past
And future
Can't change the past
Past
And future
Live for the future
何だかどうして
Somehow, why is it
未来に難
That the future is difficult?
遭難の予感がして
I have a feeling of distress.
もう随分生きてる
I've been alive for so long,
価値観だってブレて縮小
Even my values are wavering and shrinking.
素敵な出来事の
There's no sign of
気配もない
Wonderful events.
残念
Too bad,
積んだ経験
The experience I've gained
因果経済化された
Has become causal economics.
死後は退屈の進化
Is the afterlife an evolution of boredom?
飽きちゃった
I'm bored of it.
ナンセンス
Nonsense,
欲張ってくガイダンス
Guidance to be greedy,
増えるコンプライアンス
Increasing compliance.
廃れてくみたい
Seems like it's going obsolete,
推測して
Guessing about it.
あれもこれも
That and this,
どれも
Everything,
同じ味がする
Tastes the same.
UNDEAD
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead yet,
終わんない負の連鎖
This unending chain of negativity.
いつの世も、過去も未来も
In any age, past or future,
今にあるんだ
It exists in the now.
生きていることを
The fact that I'm alive,
愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill it honestly.
目指せ Happy End！
Aim for a Happy End!
UNDEAD
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead yet,
お前似てるんだ
You resemble me.
幸せを諦めてしまうな
Don't give up on happiness,
人であるんだ
Because you are human.
ただ苦しみに慣れて
Just getting used to the pain,
耐えているだけじゃ
And just enduring it...
死んでるも同然
Is as good as being dead.
屍のUNDEAD！
A corpse's UNDEAD!
教えてもっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about you,
Tell me ya more more
聞かせてもっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice,
Let me ya more more
こんなドキドキ 抑えきれない
I can't suppress this heart-pounding feeling.
Oh I need you
友達は卒業
Graduating from being just friends,
運命の私 見つけて欲しいな
I want you to find the destined me.
見つめる作戦
Staring strategy.
見つめ合えば Fall in Love
If we stare at each other, we'll fall in love.
止められない
Can't stop it.
Yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this love, this affection.
Melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melty, I'm going to melt.
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling.
今日だけ
Just for today...
大好き
...I love you.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
メルちゃん！
Mel-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント！
Choco Mint!
よりも、あ・な・た！
More than that, I like YOU!
プルルちゃん！
Pururu-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりも、あ・な・た！
More than Strawberry Flavor, I like YOU!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりも、あ・な・た！
More than Cookie & Cream, I like YOU!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き Ice Cream！
Of course we love Ice Cream!
止められない yeah yeah yeah
Can't stop it yeah yeah yeah.
この恋この愛で
With this love, this affection.
Melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melty, I'm going to melt.
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling.
今日だけ
Just for today...
大好き
...I love you.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
お願い 見つけて My Darling
Please, find me, my darling.
お願い 気づいて My Darling
Please, notice me, my darling.
勇気を出して
Summon your courage.
近づく作戦
Approach strategy.
手と手が触れて
When our hands touch...
Fall in Love
...we'll fall in love.
止められない
Can't stop it.
Yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this love, this affection.
Melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melty, I'm going to melt.
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling.
今日だけ
Just for today...
大好き
...I love you.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
Ai Ai Ice Cream
Scream 叫びましょう
Scream, let's shout it out.
スクリーム Ai Scream
Scream, Ai Scream.
La la la...
あ～、元気もらえて面白くって、オレンジで...
Ah, getting energy, it's funny, it's orange...
...シャンパンコール得意な人、いないかな？
...is there anyone around who's good at champagne calls?
それ俺やないかーい！
That's gotta be me!
イケナイ太陽
Ikenai Taiyo (Naughty Sun)
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
チョットでいいから見せてくれないか
Won't you show me just a little?
お前のセクシー・フェロモンでオレ メロメロ
I'm head over heels for your sexy pheromones.
Ah ふれちゃいそう でも イケナイの
Ah, it looks like we'll touch, but we can't.
徐々に高なる鼓動 止められないわ
I can't stop my heart from beating faster and faster.
交わす言葉の記憶 遠く
The memory of words exchanged is far away.
口元の動きに揺れ動く
Swaying to the movement of your mouth.
濡れた...
Wet...
ABC 続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue,
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
that just won't do, will it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep down, it's different, isn't it?
俺の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't just that,
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out passionately deep inside!
きっと君じゃなきゃヤダよ
Surely, I don't want anyone but you!
俺はイケナイ太陽
I am the sinful sun.
Na na na na na na na na na
赤い糸なんて絵空事
The red string of fate is just a pipe dream,
でも下心でさえ信じたいの
but I want to believe even in ulterior motives.
俺は正しい
I am right,
君も正しい
you are also right,
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
anyway, I won't be swayed anymore!
騙し騙され
Deceiving and being deceived,
胸疼く
my chest aches.
下手な芝居がより盛り上げる夜
A clumsy act livens up the night even more.
息が耳に触れた二人 AH
Breaths touched our ears, the two of us, AH!
ABC 続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue,
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
that just won't do, will it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep down, it's different, isn't it?
私の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't just that,
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out passionately deep inside!
きっと君じゃなきゃヤダよ
Surely, I don't want anyone but you!
私イケナイ太陽
I am the sinful sun.
交わす言葉の記憶と
The memories of the words we exchanged,
口元の動きに揺れ動く
and the movement of your lips make me tremble.
濡れた髪を撫でたそして AH
I stroked your wet hair and then, AH!
ABC 続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue,
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
that just won't do, will it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep down, it's different, isn't it?
俺の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't just that,
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out passionately deep inside!
きっと君じゃなきゃヤダよ
Surely, I don't want anyone but you!
俺はイケナイ太陽
I am the sinful sun.
絡み合う糸は君と
The intertwining thread is with you,
俺を結ぶ赤い糸
the red thread that ties me.
Na na na na na na na na na
みんな、来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for coming!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ということで、お友達が来てくれたので、
So, since my friends came by,
自己紹介してもらうと思います！
I'd like to have them introduce themselves!
まずはプルルちんから！
First up, Pururu-chin!
はーい！
Haaai!
おはプル！
Ohapuru!
天使と悪魔のハーフ、プルプルエンジェルデビル...
Half Angel and Devil, Puru-Puru Angel Devil...
兎々神プルルだよ！
I'm Totogami Pururu!
アキぷぢちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Aki-puji-chan, Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so muuuch!
いや、とっても楽しかったね！
Man, that was really fun!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして続いて、カルビちゃん！
And next, Karubi-chan!
はーい！
Haaai!
お肉の国のお姫様、赤見かるびです！
The Princess of the Meat Kingdom, Akami Karubi!
アキロゼ！誕生日おめでとう！
AkiRose! Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いいね、ライブって。
Lives shows are nice, huh.
友達とライブ初めてだからさ、
It's my first Live with friends,
マジで嬉しかったよ。
so I was seriously happy.
ありがとう呼んでくれて。
Thanks for inviting me.
いえいえ！
Don't mention it!
またやろうぜ！
Let's do it again!
やろう！
Let's do it!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
そして最後に、ズズさん！
And finally, Zuzu-san!
はーい！
Haaai!
僕のこと知らない人いると思うんで、
I think there are people who don't know me,
自己紹介だけさせてください！
so please let me just introduce myself!
雨降ってザーザー
Rain falls Zaa-Zaa,
少女時代はGee Gee
Girls' Generation is Gee Gee!
俺の名前はズズズズズ！
My name is Zuzu Zuzu Zuzu!
ズズでございます！
I am Zuzu!
いや、お誕生日おめでとう！
Well, Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ありがとう！
ありがとう！バイバイ！
Thank you! Bye bye!
あー、賑やかで楽しかった！
Ah, that was lively and fun!
まるで...
It's almost...
この世界で二人だけみたいだね
...as if we're the only two in this world.
なんて少しだけ
I just dreamed...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...a little dream, that's all.
つま先に月明かり あなたの香り
Moonlight on my toes, your scent...
指に触れる指
Fingers touching fingers.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I have to go now.
なにもかも忘れて
Forgetting everything.
ガラスの上を裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on the glass.
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
With every pain, blood flows and falls.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come find me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
A goldfish released into a rusted pool.
くずかごの中隠した林檎
An apple hidden in the wastebasket.
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡
Scars remaining on your withered skin.
犬のように泳いだ迷子
A lost child swimming like a dog.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
(どこにいるよ)
(Where are you?)
何をしてるの
What are you doing?
(ここ見てるよ)
(I'm looking right here.)
この世 間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
そばにいてよ
Stay by my side.
遊びに来いよ
Come play with me.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on the glass.
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
With every pain, blood flows and falls.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come find me.
まるで...
It's almost...
この世界で二人だけみたいだね
...as if we're the only two in this world.
なんて少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
I just dreamed a little dream, that's all.
さあ、選択の時だ
Now, it is time to choose.
コイン？
A coin?
このコインは...
This coin is...
ああ、そうか。
Ah, I see.
君はそっちなんだね。
So you're on that side, huh?
ここに座って。
Sit here.
え？
Eh?
この後は...君次第だよ。
What happens next... is up to you.
忘れられないのはこの目のせい
It's this eye's fault I can't forget
赤く残る過ち甘噛みの跡
The red remaining mistake, traces of a playful bite
溢れ出す愛は止め処もない
Overflowing love is endless
誰もいない間に
While no one is around
悪魔を探す
Searching for the devil
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is this ear's fault
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling from within the deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して
Break out of this cage
悪魔は賭ける
The devil bets
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, it's this mouth's fault
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
Nights where I bite back even the words I want to convey
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't confess yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God to spend time with the devil
曖昧みー夢見ていたいあなたに
Ambiguous me, I want to keep dreaming of you
そっと気付かせてあげたいだけ
I just want to let you realize softly
Oh あなたにも
Oh, to you too
消えないmy傷を隠したい
I want to hide my unvanishing wound
あなたにそっと悩ませてあげたいだけ
I just want to let you worry softly
Oh あなたにも
Oh, to you too
Oh...
悪魔を探す
Searching for the devil
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is this ear's fault
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling from within the deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して
Break out of this cage
悪魔は賭ける
The devil bets
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, it's this mouth's fault
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
Nights where I bite back even the words I want to convey
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't confess yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God to spend time with the devil
好き嫌い常識 I don't care ぶっ飛べば
Love, hate, common sense, I don't care, if I fly away
高々運命 Majority あたしに敗けは無し
Mere fate, majority, I have no defeat
ここまでって引かれたその Border 誰の Rule
Who's rule is that border drawn saying 'up to here'
あの日乗り越えた Weak Heart
The weak heart I overcame that day
強くなったあたしが笑い飛ばしてあげる
I, who became strong, will laugh it off for you
言いたいことは言う
I say what I want to say
やりたくないことはしない
I don't do what I don't want to do
悪意気にしない
I don't care about malice
みんな違うの当然だし
It's natural that everyone is different
あたしは変わらない
I won't change
ぐうの音も出ない
Speechless
Everybody say I want to be free
言い訳などは言わない それじゃ何も変えられない
I don't make excuses, that won't change anything
Everybody say I want to be free
守りたい自分肯定
Affirm the self I want to protect
生きてるんだ
I am living
Everybody say I want to be free
生まれた
Born
育った
Raised
選んできたんだ
I chose this
思い出せ
Remember
あたしはあたしだ
I am me
他の誰でもない
Not anyone else
何ひとつもない
Nothing at all
嘘じゃない
Not a lie
なりたい自分に
To the self I want to be
好き嫌い常識 I don't care ぶっ飛べば
Love, hate, common sense, I don't care, if I fly away
あどけなくぶっ飛べば
If I fly away innocently
フルテン鳴らし
Crank it up to full ten
このリリックかまし
Drop these lyrics
わからす挑発
Provoke to make them understand
舌抜いて舌打ち狩るのハート
Pull out the tongue, click the tongue, hunt the heart
聞かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it.
やってやるから考えな
I'll do it, so you better think.
アタシがついてるから
Because I'm with you.
Everybody say I want to be free
Quiet! この美徳習慣 全部黙らす Shhh
Quiet! These virtues and customs, I'll silence them all. Shhh.
水増し表記の Wicked Wicked
Inflated numbers, Wicked Wicked.
生きてるんだし
I'm alive, after all.
ねぇ 生きてるんだし
Hey, I'm alive, after all.
生まれたその時から 選んできたんだ
From the moment I was born, I've been choosing.
思い出せ
Remember.
アタシはアタシだ
I am me.
不可能のことなど 何一つもない
There is nothing impossible.
そうじゃないの？
Isn't that right?
生まれたその時から 選んできたんだ
From the moment I was born, I've been choosing.
思い出せ
Remember.
あなたはあなただ
You are you.
不可能のことなど 何一つもない
There is nothing impossible.
そうじゃないの？
Isn't that right?
なりたい自分に
To the self I want to become.
好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹き飛ばせば
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, just blow them away.
Again 好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹き飛ばせば
Again, likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, just blow them away.
流れてく時の中ででも
Even within the flowing time.
気だるさがほらグルグル廻って
Look, the listlessness spins round and round.
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart drifting away from me.
そう知らない
That's right, I don't know.
自分から動くこともなく
Without moving on my own accord.
時の隙間に流され続けて
Continuously swept away in the gaps of time.
知らないわ周りのことなど
I don't know anything about my surroundings.
私は私それだけ
I am me, that's all.
夢見てる？なにも見てない？
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing nothing?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
Even my own words are useless to speak.
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ
Feeling sad only makes me tired.
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
I should just spend time feeling nothing.
戸惑う言葉与えられても
Even if I'm given confusing words.
自分の心ただ上の空
My heart is just absent-minded.
もし私から動くのならば
If I were to move on my own.
すべて変えるのなら黒にする
If I'm to change everything, I'll turn it black.
こんな自分に未来はあるの？
Is there a future for someone like me?
こんな世界に私はいるの？
Do I exist in a world like this?
今切ないの？今悲しいの？
Am I in pain now? Am I sad now?
自分の事もわからないまま
While not even understanding myself.
歩むことさえ疲れるだけよ
Even walking is just tiring.
人のことなど知りもしないわ
I don't even know about other people.
こんな私も変われるのなら
If even someone like me can change.
もし変われるのなら白になる
If I can change, I'll become white.
流れてく時の中ででも
Even within the flowing time.
気だるさがほらグルグル廻って
Look, the listlessness spins round and round.
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart drifting away from me.
そう知らない
That's right, I don't know.
自分から動くこともなく
Without moving on my own accord.
時の隙間に流され続けて
Continuously swept away in the gaps of time.
知らないわ周りのことなど
I don't know anything about my surroundings.
私は私それだけ
I am me, that's all.
夢見てる？なにも見てない？
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing nothing?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
Even my own words are useless to speak.
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ
Feeling sad only makes me tired.
…だけよ
…just that.
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
I should just spend my time feeling nothing.
戸惑う言葉与えられても
Even if I'm given confusing words,
自分の心ただ上の空
My heart remains absent-minded.
もし私から動くのならば
If I were to move on my own,
すべて変えるのなら黒にする
If I change everything, I'll turn it black.
動くのならば　動くのならば
If I move, if I move,
すべて壊すわ　すべて壊すわ
I'll destroy everything, I'll destroy everything.
悲しむならば　悲しむならば
If I grieve, if I grieve,
私の心　白く変われば
If my heart turns white,
あなたのことも　私のことも
Even you, even me,
すべてのことも　まだ知らないの
And everything else... I still don't know.
重い目蓋を開けたのならば
If I open my heavy eyelids,
すべて壊すのなら黒になれ
If I'm to destroy everything, turn black!
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
Someday, the light of love you kindle in your eyes
時を超えて
Will transcend time,
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
The dream of a world rushing to ruin,
確かに一つ
Surely, one thing,
壊すだろう
Will destroy it.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Swallowing down hesitation,
君が望むものは何？
What is it that you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
At the destination of such greedy longing,
儚い明日はあるの？
Is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
I saw it in my dreams as a child,
古の魔法のように
Like ancient magic,
闇さえ砕く力で
With power to smash even darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to see you smiling.
怯えるこの手の中には
Inside these trembling hands,
手折られた花と勇気
A plucked flower and courage.
想いだけが頼るすべて
My feelings are the only thing I rely on,
光を呼び覚ます
Awakening the light,
願い
A wish.
いつか君も誰かの為に
Someday, you too, for someone's sake,
強い力を望むのだろう
Will wish for strong power.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
On the night love seized your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれて来る
Unknown words will be born.
迷わずに行けるなら
If I can go without wavering,
心が砕けてもいいわ
I don't mind if my heart breaks.
いつも目の前の悲しみに
To face the sadness always before my eyes,
立ち向かう為の
I want a spell...
呪文が欲しい
...to stand against it.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are a memory still dreaming,
私は眠らない明日
I am a sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
To win the miracle of us meeting,
勝ち取る為に進むわ
I will move forward.
怯えるこの手の中には
Inside these trembling hands,
手折られた花と刃
A plucked flower and a blade.
想いだけが生きるすべて
My feelings are all that live,
心に振りかざす
Brandishing in my heart...
願い
A wish.
囚われた太陽の輝く日へ
To the day the captured sun shines.
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
When I liked books about Wonderland.
願いはきっと叶うと
That wishes will surely come true,
教えるお伽噺を信じた
I believed the fairy tales that taught me so.
光と影の中
In the light and shadow.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Quietly blooming in profusion,
古の魔法優しく
Ancient magic gently,
世界を変える力が
Whispers that the power to change the world
その手にあると囁く
Is within those hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream an endless dream,
君と行く時の中で
In the time I go with you.
想いだけが生きる全て
Only feelings are everything that lives.
命を作るのは
What creates life is...
願い
A wish.
わぁー！
Wuaaa!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！ イェイ！
Thank you! Yay!
うー！
Woo!
今日は来てくれてありがとうございます
Thanks for coming today.
こちらこそですよ
The pleasure is ours.
呼んでくれてありがとう
Thanks for inviting us.
実はね、二人を呼んだのはちょっと理由があって
Actually, there's a reason I invited you two.
お？なんだなんだ？
Oh? What is it?
前にアキロゼの4周年の時に
Before, at Akiroze's 4th anniversary,
3人でKalafinaさんの曲出させてもらったんだけど
The three of us performed a Kalafina song.
やりましたね
We did.
めっちゃ良かったやつね
That was really good.
ハーモニーがね
The harmony was...
ミオちゃんの歌も大好きだし、AZKiちゃんの歌も大好きだし
I love Mio-chan's singing, and I love AZKi-chan's singing...
もうそこね、忘れられないの、本当に
I really can't forget that moment.
わかる
I understand.
めっちゃわかる
Totally understand.
だからもう一回、ライブステージで3人で歌いたくて、今日は来てもらいました
So I wanted to sing with the three of us on a live stage one more time, so I had you come today.
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
だからこれからは、これを機に、もっと何か3人で歌ったりとか
So from now on, taking this opportunity, I hope we can sing more together...
なんかそういうの挑戦できたらめっちゃ嬉しいななんて
I'd be really happy if we could challenge things like that.
いいですか？
Is that okay?
このハーモニーを重ねていきましょうよ
Let's keep layering these harmonies.
え、いいの？ 嬉しい！
Eh, really? I'm happy!
なんかユニット名とか欲しいな
I kind of want a unit name.
確かに欲しいな
I certainly want one.
え、なんだろう？
Eh, what would it be?
なんかちょっと世界目指せるぐらいのさ
Something that could aim for the world...
世界！？
The world!?
世界のコンサートをしようよ
Let's do a world concert.
やりたいね
I want to do that.
世界に轟く何かをね
Something that roars across the world...
もう3人でライブとか、なんかアコースティックとか
A live with the three of us, or something acoustic...
なんかオーケストラライブとか
Or an orchestra live...
わ、良くないですか？
Wow, isn't that good?
そんなことをしてみたい
I want to try doing things like that.
我らならできるかもしれない！
We might be able to do it!
やった！お願いします
Yay! Please.
あれ？これはいったい何ですか？
Huh? What on earth is this?
もしかして...このライブでみんなからの...なんかいいパワーで
Could it be... with some good power from everyone at this live...
なんか今来てる
Something is coming now.
いいのあるじゃんそれ、何だよそのパワー
That's a good one. What is that power?
こちらがなんと完成しました！
This has surprisingly been completed!
なんだそれ！？
What is that!?
実は...この後、アキロゼの新曲が...出ます！
Actually... after this, Akiroze's new song... will be released!
わぁー！ 出たー！ 来たー！
Wow! It's out! It's here!
こちら、まぁ今回のライブのまぁテーマというか...
This is, well, the theme of this live, or rather...
壮大なテーマがあるんですけれども
It has a grand theme, but...
そちらが詰まったような楽曲になっています
It's a song packed with that.
そしてライブ終わりの日付が変わる時にリリースしますので是非聴いてください
And it will be released when the date changes after the live ends, so please listen to it.
聴いてね！
Listen to it!
みんな聴くぞ！
Everyone listen!
ではでは、じゃあ次の曲に行きますか？
Well then, shall we go to the next song?
次の曲？
Next song?
新曲のお披露目...
New song reveal...
なんだって！？
What did you say!?
しちゃいます！
I'll do it!
わぁー！
Wow!
え、今からってこと？
Eh, you mean right now?
今から...頑張ります
From now... I'll do my best.
もう最後まで見逃せないですね
Can't miss it until the very end.
楽しみだ
Looking forward to it.
お願いします
Please.
じゃあアキちゃん頑張ってね！
Then Aki-chan, good luck!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
またね！
See you!
頑張り、頑張り
Do your best, do your best.
頑張るよー！
I'll do my best!
魅惑の言葉の裏面に忍ばせた
Hidden on the flip side of bewitching words,
1mgのスパイス
1mg of spice.
たちまち華麗な指先で彩る
Instantly colored by magnificent fingertips,
本日のダイス
Today's dice.
当たり見て妥協してちゃ
If you compromise after seeing the win,
生き残れないでしょう
You won't be able to survive.
率直に言ってその全てが欲しい
Frankly speaking, I want it all.
一人勝ちオールイン
Sole winner, all-in.
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
Who cares what happens?
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, are there?
翻弄して翻弄されてゾクゾク
Toying with you, being toyed with, it's thrilling.
食らっちゃっても本望でしょ
Even if you take a hit, it's what you wanted.
最低だって滾るでしょ
Even at the worst, it gets your blood boiling.
見透かして見透かされてイェーイ
Seeing through, being seen through, yeah.
終わりはない
There is no end.
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
This throbbing heart is all nonfiction.
嗜むはずでも
Even if I'm supposed to just dabble,
たまには飲み過ぎて
Sometimes I drink too much.
1回休み
Miss a turn.
周りもそわつく
Those around me get restless,
思わぬうたた寝で
From an unexpected nap.
2回休み
Miss two turns.
切れる頭と勘だけじゃ
Just a sharp mind and intuition
手に入らないもの
Aren't enough to get what I want.
そこでいて見惚れるならいい
Stay there if you're just going to admire.
命懸けで楽しむわ
I'll enjoy this with my life on the line.
Yeah yeah yeah
天地は案外近いのに
Heaven and earth are surprisingly close,
この距離 命乞い
This distance, begging for life.
たかがモノポリー されど道理
It's just Monopoly, but it's the truth.
秘める想いで今宵も
With hidden feelings, tonight too,
私は強い
I am strong.
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
Who cares what happens?
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, are there?
翻弄して翻弄されてゾクゾク
Toying with you, being toyed with, it's thrilling.
食らっちゃっても本望でしょ
Even if you take a hit, it's what you wanted.
最低だって滾るでしょ
Even at the worst, it gets your blood boiling.
見透かして見透かされてイェーイ
Seeing through, being seen through, yeah.
終わりはない
There is no end.
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
This throbbing heart is all nonfiction.
落ちても昇ってもノンフィクション
Falling or rising, it's nonfiction.
中川に浮かぶ 夕日をめがけて
Aiming for the setting sun floating on the Nakagawa,
小石を蹴ったら 靴まで飛んで
When I kicked a pebble, my shoe flew off too,
ジョギングしていた 大工の頭に
Hitting the head of a carpenter who was jogging,
ガキのまんまだと 笑われたのさ
He laughed and said I'm still a brat.
どこかに元気を 落っことしても
Even if I drop my energy somewhere,
葛飾亀有 アクビをひとつ
Katsushika Kameari, let out a yawn.
変わらない町並みが 妙に優しいよ
The unchanging townscape is strangely kind.
中央広場で 子供の手を引く
Leading a child by the hand in the central square,
太ったあの子は 初恋の人
That chubby girl is my first love.
ゴンパチ池で 渡したラブレター
The love letter I gave her at Gonpachi Pond,
今も持てると からかわれたよ
She teased me saying she still has it.
何もいいこと なかったけど
Nothing good really happened, but...
葛飾水元 流れる雲と
Katsushika Mizumoto, with the flowing clouds.
ラプソディー口ずさみ 少し歩こうか
Shall we walk a bit while humming a rhapsody?
カラスが鳴くから もう日が暮れるね
The crows are cawing, so the sun is setting.
焼き鳥ほおばり ビール飲もうか
Let's stuff ourselves with yakitori and drink beer.
とんがり帽子の 取水塔から
From the pointy-hat water intake tower,
帝釈天へと 夕日が落ちる
The sun sets towards Taishakuten.
隠したものをこうして終わるんだね
Things we've hidden, this is how they end, isn't it?
隠し歌詞はまた幸せだって
The hidden lyrics say 'happiness' again.
無くして気が付いた バカな本音だから
I realized it after losing it, because it's a foolish true feeling.
何処かに元気を落っことしても
Even if I drop my energy somewhere,
可視化 亀有 アクビを一つ
Visualization, Kameari, a single yawn.
変わらない街並みが妙に優しいや
The unchanging cityscape is strangely kind.
アキロゼ生誕祭2026をご覧の皆さん、
To everyone watching Akirose Birthday Festival 2026,
いかがでしたでしょうか？
how was it?
さてここからは、大事なお知らせがあるので、
Now, from here on, I have an important announcement,
最後までしっかり聞いていってね。
so please listen carefully until the end.
まずはお知らせ一つ目。
First, announcement number one.
アキ・ローゼンタール2026誕生日グッズ発売です！
Aki Rosenthal 2026 Birthday Goods are on sale!
今回は、ライブの世界観をぎゅっと
This time, I worked hard to produce goods...
楽しんでもらえるグッズを頑張って制作いたしました。
...that let you fully enjoy the world of this live.
なので、今回のライブが良かったなーって思った方は
So, for those who thought this live was good,
是非応援で購入していただくのも凄く嬉しいです。
I'd be very happy if you supported me by buying them.
それではまず一つ目のグッズ。
So, first, the first item.
Life is GAME ラバーマット。
Life is GAME Rubber Mat.
今回のイラストはLAM先生に描き下ろしていただきました。
LAM-sensei drew the illustration for this.
素敵なイラストありがとうございます。
Thank you for the wonderful illustration.
今回のライブの世界観をイメージしたイラストになっています。
It's an illustration imagining the live's world view.
めちゃくちゃセクシーで色っぽいけど、
It features an Akirose who is super sexy and sensual,
カッコいいようなアキロゼになっています。
but also cool at the same time.
ラバーマットで思う存分楽しんでください。
Please enjoy it to your heart's content with the mat.
ちなみにサイズはカードゲームにピッタリ。
By the way, the size is perfect for card games.
この意味わかるよね？
You understand what this means, right?
二つ目のグッズが...
The second item is...
運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット。
The 5 Cards of Fate Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set.
アキロゼがあなたのことを占って背中を押してあげます。
Akirose will tell your fortune and give you a push.
一日の始まりや、何か運命を託したいみたいな、
At the start of the day or when you want to entrust your fate,
そんな時に使って楽しむ。
use it in times like that to enjoy.
そして5枚バーンって飾っておけるので、
And since you can display all 5 cards like 'bam',
見ても楽しめるようになっております。
it's made so you can enjoy looking at them too.
占い方法は、この後紹介する
The fortune-telling method is linked with...
アキロゼのASMRボイスと連動しております。
...Akirose's ASMR Voice which I'll introduce later.
飾っても楽しい、使っても楽しい。
Fun to display, fun to use.
そのような連動グッズになっているので、是非ゲットしてください。
It's that kind of linked item, so please get it.
続いてのグッズは... アキロゼのトランプ！
The next item is... Akirose's Playing Cards!
作っちゃいました！
I made them!
こちら実際に遊んでいただけるトランプなので、
Since these are cards you can actually play with,
たくさん予備も買った方がいいんじゃないかなと思います。
I think it might be better to buy lots of spares too.
是非トランプでもアキロゼをたくさん楽しんでアピールもしてくださいね。
Please enjoy Akirose with the cards and show them off.
続いてはこちら。アキロゼのカードケース。
Next is this. Akirose's Card Case.
ホロカはもちろんトランプなど小物を入れても大丈夫です。
For Holo Cards of course, but small items fit too.
是非お家や持ち歩きに使ってね。
Please use it at home or for carrying around.
そしてボイスの紹介です。
And now, the introduction of the Voice.
今回もASMRボイスを特別に発売。
This time too, I'm specially selling ASMR Voice.
アキとロゼがそれぞれ左右からあなたのことを誘惑しちゃうかも。
Aki and Rose might seduce you from the left and right.
台本も頑張って書いたので、
I worked hard writing the script too,
是非是非たっぷり楽しんでもらったら嬉しいです。
so I'd be happy if you enjoyed it thoroughly.
こちらボイスは『Life is GAME ～アキとロゼの盤上～』、
This Voice, with 'Life is GAME ~On the Board of Aki and Rose~'...
こちらをメインとし、
...as the main part,
ASMRショートボイスとして先ほどの
contains ASMR Short Voices linked to...
運命の5枚タロット風アクリルカードと連動したショートボイスが入っております。
...the 5 Cards of Fate Tarot-style Acrylic Cards from earlier.
ショートボイスのシャッフルランダム再生をして、
Play the Short Voices on shuffle random,
選ばれたボイスがあなたの運命の一枚になります。
and the chosen voice becomes your card of fate.
是非いろいろ楽しんでね。
Please enjoy it in various ways.
これらのグッズ全てが詰まったフルセット購入にはなんと特典も付いております。
Buying the Full Set with everything includes a bonus.
今回のキービジュアルのイラストを使ったチケット風カードになっております。
It's a ticket-style card using the key visual illustration.
あなたはこのゲームに参加する？参加しない？
Will you participate in this game? Or not?
こちらもライブの世界観を高めるアイテムになっているので是非ゲットしてください。
This item also enhances the world view, so please get it.
そして数量限定あります。
And there is a limited quantity version.
直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ったものになっております。
It has a handwritten autograph and foil-stamped message.
頑張って書きます。
I will do my best to write them.
そして数量限定が終わり次第、
And once the limited quantity ends,
箔押しでの複製サインとメッセージが入ったチケット風カードになります。
it'll be a card with a foil-stamped autograph and message.
是非フルセット購入特典ゲットしてね。
Please get the Full Set purchase bonus.
大事な発売時間は、この後21時30分。
The important sale time is after this at 21:30.
21時30分にショップオープンです。
The shop opens at 21:30.
是非登録など準備して備えておいてね。
Please prepare by registering and get ready.
続きましてお知らせ二つ目。
Continuing on, announcement number two.
この後21時45分からメンバー限定のアフターライブを行います。
After this, from 21:45, I will hold a member-only After Live.
ライブ本編とはまた違う楽曲を披露する予定なので
I plan to perform songs different from the main live,
是非お楽しみに。
so please look forward to it.
今日メンバーになった方も是非是非見てね。
Those who became members today, please watch it.
ちなみに過去のライブのメンバー限定アフターライブも見れちゃうと思うので、
By the way, I think you can also watch past After Lives,
是非その辺も楽しんでね。
so please enjoy those as well.
ちなみに、今回のサムネイルイラストは...
By the way, regarding today's thumbnail illustration...
メンバー限定で壁紙としてプレゼント予定です。
...we plan to gift it as a wallpaper for members only.
お楽しみにー！
Look forward to it!
そして！お知らせ３つ目！
And! The third announcement!
本日の生誕祭ライブの後も...
Even after today's birthday live...
お楽しみはまだまだ続きます。
...the fun is just getting started.
なんと！ホロアースにて特別企画。
Surprisingly! A special project in HoloEarth.
アキ・ローゼンタール生誕祭2026...
Aki Rosenthal Birthday Festival 2026...
...アンコール in ホロアース...
...Encore in HoloEarth...
...を開催しまーす。
...will be held!
今回初披露した新曲『Monopoly』を...
The new song 'Monopoly' unveiled for the first time today...
...ホロアースで歌っちゃいます。
...I will sing it in HoloEarth!
いろんな角度からアキロゼのパフォーマンスや...
From various angles, please take a good look...
...演出をじっくりと見てみてくださいね。
...at AkiRose's performance and the production.
さらに、ホロアースだけのMCパートも...
Furthermore, since there will be plenty of MC parts...
...たっぷりやるので、ぜひぜひ会いに来てください。
...exclusive to HoloEarth, please definitely come to see me.
開催日は3月13日...
The date is March 13th...
3月13日です。
It is March 13th.
詳細はホロアース公式Xをチェックしてね。
Please check the HoloEarth official X for details.
そして、最後のお知らせが...
And, the final announcement is...
新曲『Monopoly』！
The new song 'Monopoly'!
本日日付が変わる頃にリリースされますので...
It will be released around midnight tonight...
各音楽配信サービスからぜひ購入してね...
...so please buy it from music streaming services...
...たくさん聴いてね。
...and listen to it a lot!
振付も歌もとってもキャッチーなので...
Both the choreography and song are very catchy...
覚えてみんなで楽しんでもらえる...
...so remember it and have everyone enjoy it...
...愛されるような楽曲になってくれたら嬉しいなーと思っています。
...I'd be happy if it becomes a song that is loved.
また後日ライブ配信で...
Also, in a later live stream...
新曲『Monopoly』だったり...
...I'd like to talk about the new song 'Monopoly'...
今回のライブに触れた後日談など語ったり...
...and share stories from this live...
一緒に見たりなどしたいなと思ってるので...
...or watch it together with you, so...
ぜひチャンネル登録、高評価ポチ、通知もオン！
Please subscribe, hit like, and turn on notifications!
忘れてた人は今ポチっとしてね。
If you forgot, click it right now.
絶対絶対また会いに来てね。
Definitely, definitely come see me again.
それでは。
Well then.
運命は時に残酷。
Fate is sometimes cruel.
あなたが選びたくて選んだものではないかもしれない。
It might not be something you chose because you wanted to.
だけど、いつでもあなたの人生はあなたのもの。
But, your life is always yours.
人生は一度きり。
Life is only once.
やり直しのきかないこのゲーム...
This game where you can't start over...
あなたは、どう楽しむ？
How will you enjoy it?
Member Only After Live